Raymond Spilman Papers
Raymond Spilman Papers
- Business files (Part I)
  - Rolled Charts and Drawings
    - Columbus Iron Works (Oversize 9)
    - Cosco, 3 items (Box 86)
    - Cosco (Oversize 2)
    - Cosco (Oversize 5)
    - Cosco (Oversize 6)
    - Cosco (Oversize 7)
    - Cosco, 2 items (Oversize 8)
    - Cosco (Oversize 9)
    - Cosco, 2 items (Oversize 10)
    - Cosco (Oversize 13)
    - Cosco (Oversize 14)
    - Cosco (Oversize 16)
    - Cosco (Oversize 17)
    - Edwards Air Force Base (Oversize 1)
    - Electro Mechanical Research (Oversize 4)
    - General Electric, 2 items (Box 86)
    - General Thrift Corporation (Oversize 14)
    - H. Schenier Offices (Oversize 5)
    - Halliwell (Box 86)
    - Halliwell (Oversize 10)
    - Halliwell, 6 items (Oversize 11)
    - Halliwell (Oversize 18)
    - Ideal Toy Company (Box 86)
    - IDL (Box 86)
    - Kollenburg (Box 86)
    - Lima Trade Fair (Oversize 1)
    - Lima Trade Fair (Oversize 2)
    - Lima Trade Fair (Oversize 12)
    - Lima Trade Fair (Oversize 16)
    - M.H. Rhodes (Oversize 11)
    - Mack Trucks (Oversize 11)
    - Major Industries (Oversize 2)
    - Maxwell House (Oversize 1)
    - Maxwell House (Oversize 4)
    - MB-1 (Oversize 6)
    - Palco (Oversize 14)
    - Pickering (Box 86)
    - Pitney Bowes (Box 86)
    - Poznan Trade Fair (Oversize 2)
    - Prepared Frisket (Oversize 17)
    - RA-3 (Oversize 16)
    - Radiation (Oversize 4)
    - Randall, 5 items (Oversize 18)
    - Safe Flight (Oversize 14)
    - Sanders (Box 86)
    - Sanders (Oversize 3)
    - Sanders (Oversize 56)
    - Seal (Oversize 15)
    - Shav Air (Box 86)
    - Shavair (Oversize 7)
    - Shavair (Oversize 11)
    - Simmons, 2 items (Box 86)
    - Simmons (Oversize 4)
    - Simmons (Oversize 5)
    - TDMS Cart (Oversize 6)
    - Teague Blueprints (Box 86)
    - TK Foods (Oversize 9)
    - TK Foods, 2 items (Oversize 17)
    - Trion (Oversize 4)
    - UC 100 (Box 86)
    - Underwood, 2 items (Oversize 1)
    - Universal Timer (Box 86)
    - USM (Oversize 10)
    - USM (Oversize 19)
    - Wearever (Box 86)
    - Wearever, 2 items (Oversize 13)
    - Wearever (Oversize 17)
    - Wearever (Oversize 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 4 items (Box 86)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 items (Oversize 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 items (Oversize 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Oversize 16)
- Financial files (Part I)
  - Bank Deposit Receipts, 1963 (Box 30)
  - Bank Loan Information File, 1958-1961 (Box 30)
  - Bank Statements, 1956-1963; 3 folders (Box 30)
  - Ralph J.T. Bauer, February 1966-September 1967 (Box 30)
  - Billing Records, 1964-1967 (Box 30)
  - Billing Work Sheets
    - December 1963-November 1965 (Box 30)
    - December 1965-June 1968 (Box 30)
    - May 1966-December 1973 (Box 30)
    - June 1966-December 1967 (Box 30)
    - July 1968-March 1971 (Box 30)
  - Bills Work Sheets, June 1962-November 1963 (Box 30)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1959-1963; 9 folders (Box 31)
  - Cash Disbursements, 1964-1967; 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Cash Receipt Records, 1964-1967 (Box 31)
  - Charge Accounts, 1946-1963 (Box 31)
  - Checking Account Statements
    - 1956, July-August (Box 31)
    - 1956, December - 1957, September, 9 folders (Box 31)
    - 1957, August-December, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - 1958, December - 1959, November, 12 folders (Box 32)
    - 1963, December - 1965, August, 20 folders (Box 32)
    - 1965, August - 1967, December, 28 folders (Box 33)
  - Check Stubs
    - 1962, February - 1964, October, 8 folders (Box 33)
    - 1964, October - 1967, November, 8 folders (Box 34)
  - Copies of Billing, 1962-1963 (Box 34)
  - Credit Card Receipts
    - Gasoline
      - American, January 1964-October 1967 (Box 34)
      - Crown, December 1961-September 1962 (Box 34)
      - Esso, January 1959-August 1967 (Box 34)
      - Gulf, November 1967-January 1968 (Box 34)
      - Mobil, September 1962-September 1964 (Box 34)
      - Shell, January 1959-November 1967 (Box 34)
      - Sunoco, June 1960-December 1967 (Box 34)
      - Texaco, July 1959-November 1967 (Box 34)
    - General
      - American Express, January 1959-December 1967; 4 folders (Box 34)
      - Diner's Club, January 1959-October 1967 (Box 34)
  - Duplicate Bills to Clients, January 1958-December 1961; 3 folders (Box 34)
  - 120 East 56th Street, 1956-1961 (Box 35)
  - Federal and State Taxes, 1946-1949; 1951-1968; 17 folders (Box 35)
  - General Bookkeeping Correspondence, 1963 (Box 35)
  - Insurance Correspondence, 1953-1963; 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Job Sheets, 1960-1963 (Box 35)
  - Ledger Summary Sheets, November 1962-November 1965; 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962 (Box 35)
  - New York State Taxes, 1958-1962 (Box 35)
  - Old Job Sheets
    - Except Simmons, 1957-1959 (Box 35)
    - Simmons, 1954-1958 (Box 35)
  - Other Paid Bills and Petty Cash, 1963 (Box 35)
  - Paid Bills
    - Leon Deran, December 1966-September 1967 (Box 35)
    - Electric, February 1959-November 1967 (Box 35)
    - Fairbanks Foto Shop, February-December 1967 (Box 35)
    - Medical (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1958-1959, 4 folders (Box 35)
      - 1959-1963, 17 folders (Box 36)
      - 1963-1967, 16 folders (Box 37)
    - Norwalk Typographers, December 1966-October 1967 (Box 37)
    - John A. Scalzi Co., December 1967-November 1967 (Box 37)
    - Silvermine Press, August 1965-September 1967 (Box 37)
    - Spellco Paint and Art Supplies, November 1966-September 1967 (Box 37)
    - Telephone
      - February 1959-November 1962, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - December 1963-November 1967, 3 folders (Box 38)
    - 3M Business Products, August 1966-October 1967 (Box 38)
    - Wicke and Lowenfeld, July 1966-December 1967 (Box 38)
    - Robert Winters, February-December 1967 (Box 38)
  - Payroll Registers, 1954-1964; 4 folders (Box 38)
  - Petty Cash Record, 1964-1967; 4 folders (Box 38)
  - Petty Cash Slips
    - January 1960-December 1965, 14 folders (Box 38)
    - January 1966-December 1967, 6 folders (Box 39)
  - Professional Aid
    - Bills, 1958-1962; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Payments and Information, 1963 (Box 39)
  - Quarterly Taxes, 1962-1967 (Box 39)
  - Charles P. Regensburg, 1960-1962 (Box 39)
  - Sales, A-Z, 1961; 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Sales Correspondence, 1962; 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Sales Correspondence, 1962 (Box 40)
  - Specialized Travel and Tours Receipts, December 1963-December 1967; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Stocks, 1958-1960 (Box 40)
  - Stop Payment Slips, 1960 (Box 40)
  - Time Sheets, 1958-1974; 18 folders (Box 40)
  - Washburn Billing, December 1959-March 1964 (Box 40)
  - Workmen's Compensation Folder, 1954-1955 (Box 40)
- Personal files (Part I)
  - Biography (Box 41)
  - Book Typescript (Box 41)
  - Car, 1958-1973 (Box 41)
  - Church (Box 41)
  - Church Letterhead, 1963
  - Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 41)
  - Eulogy (Box 41)
  - General, 1952-1962; 8 folders (Box 41)
  - Invention, 1947 (Box 41)
  - Mayor's Conference (Box 41)
  - Memorabilia (Box 41)
  - Memorabilia (Oversize 57)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960-1961; 1965-1974; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 41)
  - Rotary (Box 41)
  - Ryder Memorial Hospital, 1973 (Box 41)
  - School Resignation, 1945-1946 (Box 41)
  - Miss Clara Spilman, 1951 (Box 41)
  - Tape and Transcription of Letter to Howard Applegate, 1971 (Box 41)
  - Thoughts on Professionalism, 1958 (Box 41)
  - Today's Hostess (Box 41)
- Correspondence (Part II)
  - Incoming, personal, undated (Box 1)
  - Outgoing, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Outgoing, drafts, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Incoming and outgoing, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
  - Designers' resumes, 1963 (Box 1)
- Subject files (Part II)
  - American Sterilizer Company, Inc. (AMSCO)
    - Correspondence and reports
      - AMS-1, 1963 (Box 1)
      - AMS-2, 1963 (Box 1)
      - AMS-2A, 1963 (Box 1)
      - AMS-3, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Old proposals, clippings
      - AMS-6, trademark, 1963 (Box 1)
      - AMS-7, S cart, 1964 (Box 1)
      - AMS-8, Satalight, 1963 (Box 1)
      - AMS-9, washer, sterilizer, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Scrub sink, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Medallion, 1963 (Box 1)
    - American Sterilizer Corp (AMSCO), 1957 (Box 4)
  - American Society of Industrial Designers
    - Annual meeting, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Board of Directors, 1962; 1963 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence
      - 1962, Jan-Sep, 2 folders (Box 2)
      - 1962, Oct - 1963, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Education, 1962-1964; 5 folders (Box 3)
    - Ethics, 1962-1963; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Holden Study and recommendations, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Inter-Society / Color Council, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Memoranda, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
    - Newsletters, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Public relations, 1961-1963 (Box 4)
    - U.S. Government Design Award, 1962 (Box 4)
    - Walter Dorwin Teague Award, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Astatic Corporation
    - Billing, 1963 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, general, 1962-1965 (Box 4)
    - AS-1, microphone, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
    - AS-2, headphone set, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Bari, Italy
    - Dec1965 - Sep 1957 (Box 5)
    - Blueprint, publication, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Finance, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
    - Trade Fair, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Becker balances, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Camera proposal, D.E.M., 1963 (Box 6)
  - Columbus Iron Works, 1959-1962; general correspondence; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Coluin, undated (Box 6)
  - Designs, various, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Dexter Folder Company, undated (Box 6)
  - Di Acro, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Dow-Jones, undated (Box 6)
  - Dursi, John Inc., undated (Box 6)
  - First Congregational Church, 1960-1963; includes color and finish swatches; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Gray Manufacturing Company, 1963; audograph, microphone. outlet photos (Box 6)
  - Halliwell, undated (Box 6)
  - Harvey-Wells Decade Unit, undated (Box 6)
  - Izmir, Zurkey, 1962; trade fair (Box 6)
  - Kaufman Design Award, 1962; press release, speeches (Box 6)
  - Larson Church, undated (Box 6)
  - Letterhead, corporations, undated (Box 6)
  - Letterhead designs, undated (Box 6)
  - Lima, Peru
    - Aerosol, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Agriculture, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Display check of lists, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Billing, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Brochures, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1959; general (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1959; with Otif (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1959; with Otif (Box 8)
    - Famous Artists Correspondence School, 1959 (Box 8)
    - General description and production script, 1959 (Box 8)
    - General fair literature, Otif, 1959 (Box 8)
    - General Motors, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Hadley School for the Blind, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Health and medical, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Irrigation, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Mary Chess, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Memo to W. Schaefer, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous memos and receipts, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Photographs, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Reports and correspondence, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Salt water converter, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Singer, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Structural information, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Television, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Tourism, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Trip to Lima, Spilman, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Union Carbide, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Westinghouse, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Woodworking, 1959 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Contract, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Designer's report, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Duplicate to send with invoice, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Proposal, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Lists, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Major industries, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Mason Motors, undated (Box 11)
  - Maxwell House Division
    - Billing, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Closure program, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Closure scheme, 1961; 1962,; undated; 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Diagrams, undated (Box 11)
    - Patent file, 1961-1962 (Box 11)
    - Prints, MHI, undated
    - Reports, 1962; copies (Box 12)
    - Reports, originals (Box 12)
    - Spare prints, 1962; undated; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1961-1962; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Medical Equipment Development Lab
    - Billing, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, general, 1955-1963 (Box 13)
    - Proposals and reports, 1960-1961 (Box 13)
  - Maynahan Bronze Co., Inc.
    - Correspondence, general, 1952-1961 (Box 13)
    - Folding bed, undated; photos (Box 13)
    - Folding bed, undated; prints (Box 13)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 13)
  - Oiljak Manufacturing Co., undated; Spark Plus Tester (Box 13)
  - Old drafting room records, to 1962 (Box 14)
  - Optical Specialties Corp., undated (Box 14)
  - Outdoor handles, WA-18, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Pennsylvania Aircraft Works, 26 Dec 1946 (Box 14)
  - Pickering Stereotone Arm PC-10, 1961
  - Poznan, Poland
    - Billing, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Standards, gen. spec, and respons., 1963 (Box 14)
    - Slide show for June, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Radiation, Inc.
    - Astronics Division, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Basford, G.M. Co., 1963 (Box 15)
    - Basic consultation contract, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Billing, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Consultation current reports, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Contract, old, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Data plates, undated (Box 15)
    - Duplicate contract, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Edwards, EE, 1959 (Box 15)
    - File TDMS equipment, 1959 (Box 15)
    - First job consultation, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Fixed stylus recorder, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Job #1297, 1959-1960 (Box 16)
    - Paint colors, radicon, Radiplex, 1959 (Box 16)
    - Photostats, undated (Box 16)
    - Prelim trademark study, undated (Box 16)
    - Prints, undated (Box 16)
    - Process stats, acetate, undated (Box 16)
    - Project subcontracts, 1958-1959 (Box 16)
    - Radicon and radiplex, 1958-1960 (Box 16)
    - Report diagrams, undated (Box 16)
    - Sketch, 1960 (Box 16)
    - TDMS telegraph distortions, undated (Box 16)
    - Trademark, undated (Box 16)
  - Rand washing machine, 1946 (Box 16)
  - Raymond Spilman office and radio, undated (Box 16)
  - Records, undated (Box 16)
  - Reliance, suppliers, quotations, financial supplier inf., gen. inf. (Box 16)
  - Reliance Manufacturing Co., 1957-1958 (Box 17)
  - Reminders and memos, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Rhodes model, Polaroid shots, 1961 (Box 17)
  - Robertshaw, Fulton
    - Billing, 1959-1960 (Box 17)
    - General file, 1959-1961 (Box 17)
  - Rochester, undated; toaster, kitchen ventilator (Box 17)
  - Rodgers Assoc., Jones and Laughlin Exec. Furniture, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Rowe Manufacturing Co.
    - General correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 17)
    - Vending machine, cigarette, undated (Box 17)
  - Royal Metal Manufacturing Co.
    - Bed negative stats, 1959 (Box 17)
    - Hospital beds, undated (Box 17)
    - Survey rough, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Proposals, reports and billing, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Security and Art Metal chairs (stats), undated
  - Shaw Air of America, Inc.
    - Billing, 1961 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, general, 1961-1963 (Box 18)
  - Sheerline desk (stats)
  - Simmons
    - 1963-1964 (Box 18)
    - Side chair, recover sketches, undated (Box 18)
  - Soundscriber Corp., 1951 (Box 18)
  - Standard-Lock Chemicals
    - Automatic paint-mixing machine carousel, 1952 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, general, 1956-1960 (Box 19)
  - Survey, undated (Box 19)
  - Surveys
    - Completed, undated (Box 19)
    - Tabulated, 1962 (Box 19)
    - Tabulated scratch sheets, 1960 (Box 19)
  - Tuennale Design entry, 29 Apr 1964 (Box 19)
  - Trion, 1961-1962; correspondence, general (Box 19)
  - Underwood Corp.
    - Correspondence, general, 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - Clay, cover, undated (Box 20)
    - Clay, portable, 1956 (Box 20)
    - Clay, standard, 1957 (Box 20)
    - Clay, standard, undated (Box 20)
    - Key tops flat portable, undated (Box 20)
    - Portable and case, 1960 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous publicity, personnel, undated (Box 20)
    - Models, undated; sketches, competition (Box 20)
    - Portable sketch photostats, 1959 (Box 20)
    - Trademark and package, undated (Box 20)
  - U.S. Rubber Co., Naugatuck Chemical Division, 1963 (Box 20)
  - Vue fax, undated (Box 20)
  - Warren, J. C. Corp., undated; tape recorder (Box 20)
  - Washburn Originals, 1954; sifters, nut chopper (Box 21)
  - Washburn Projects, undated (Box 21)
  - Zagreb
    - Correspondence, general, 1956 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 21)
    - Trade fair, 1956; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Trade fair, Yugoslavia, 1956 (Box 21)
- Manuscripts (Part II)
  - Address, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Notes, drawings, undated (Box 1)
- Printed material (Part II)
  - Advertisement, 1952-1961 (Box 1)
  - Article by Spilman, 1952 (Box 1)
  - Design manual, undated (Box 1)
  - Interview with Spilman, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 1)
  - Typewriter studies, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Typewriter studies (oversize), 1957
  - Variety store merchandizer, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
- Published material (Part II)
  - Magazine articles and gallery notes, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Reference catalogs and manuals, 1962-1963
    - AMSCO Excel (Box 2)
    - Lighting for the hospital by AMSCO (Box 2)
    - Processing analysis, AMSCO (Box 2)
    - Sterilizers and allied equipment catalog, office copy (Box 2)
    - Supply and apparatus inventories for St. Vincent's Hospital, Toledo, Ohio (Box 2)
  - Surgical tables, lights, and furniture catalogs
    - Vacamatic Sterilizer maintenance (Box 2)
    - Wilmot castle company material (Box 2)
- Spilman Designs (Part II)
  - Bari Trade Fair, 1957 (Box 1)
  - Columbus Iron Works, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Glazer-Steers Record Chamber, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Itek Corps identity program, 1959 (Box 1)
  - Lilliston mower designs, 7 Dec 1961 (Box 1)
  - Lilliston peanut combine, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Maxwell House Coffee can, 1961-1962; miscellaneous drawings (Box 1)
  - Maynahan Bronze, Ludini applications, Soudy-Survey, folding bed-springs (Box 1)
  - Poznan Color Plates, undated (Box 1)
  - Radiation Inc.
    - Deced. jobs, 1958-1960 (Box 1)
    - Interior systems cabinetry (told to rephotograph), undated (Box 1)
  - Rhoades, H. H. parking meters, undated (Box 1)
  - Simmons contract furniture, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Spilman, Raymond offices, 1962 (Box 1)
  - Washburn outdoor lines, to 1960 (Box 1)
- Books
  - Papadaki, Stamo / Oscar Miemeyer: Works In Progress Reinhold Publishing Corporation, New York: 1956 (Box 1)
  - Skawonius, Sven Erik / Kontur 8 Esselte AB, Stockholm, Sweden: 1959 (Box 1)
  - Wallace, Don / Shaping America’s Products Reinhold Publishing Corporation, New York: 1956 (Box 1)
  - Wolfe, Jeremy M. / The Mind’s Eye W.H. Freeman and Company, New York: 1976 (Box 1)
  - Hope, Augustine and Margaret Walch / The Color Compendium Van Nostrand Reinhold Company, New York: 1970 (Box 1)
  - Itten, Johannes / The Elements of Color Van Nostrand Reinhold Company, New York: 1970 (Box 1)
  - Teague, Walter Dorwin / Pencil Points, September 1937 Design: 1937 (Box 1)
  - Virshup, Evelyn / A Compilation of Feelings By Right Brain People In A Left Brain World Art Therapy West: 1978 (Box 1)
  - Dreyfuss, Henry / Industrial Design Volume 5 Comet Press Inc.: 1957, signed Copy (Box 1)
  - Industrial Design: Special International Issue Whitney Publications, Inc.: 1960 (Box 1)
  - Bayley, Stephen / The Conran Directory of Design Villard Books, New York: 1985 (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Edward Deming and Faith Andrews / Shaker Furniture Dover Publications, Inc., New York: 1937 (Box 1)
  - Friedman, William / 20th Century Design: USA 1959 (Box 1)
  - Glass, Henry P. / The Shape of Manmade Things E.C.G. Publishers, Northfield, IL: 1996, signed Copy (Box 1)
  - Geddes, Norman Bel / Horizons Dover Publications, Inc., New York: 1932 (Box 1)
  - Rewald, John / Post-Impressionism from Van Gogh to Gaugin The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1956 (Box 1)
  - Asimow, Morris / Introduction to Design Prentice-Hall, Inc., Englewood Cliffs, NJ: 1962 (Box 1)
  - Dibner, Bern / Heralds of science M.I.T. Press, Cambridge, MA: 1969 (Box 1)
  - Maldonado, Tomas / Max Bill Nueva Vision, Buenos Aires, Argentina: 1955 (Box 1)
  - Terre Des Hommes: Man and His World Canadian Corporation: 1967 (Box 1)
  - Stone, Irving / Lust for Life Pocket Books, Inc., New York: 1945 (Box 2)
  - Stone, Irving / The Agony and the Ecstasy New American Library of World Literature, Inc., 1961 (Box 2)
  - Fuller, E. Buckminster / How Little I Know 1966 (Box 2)
  - The Museum of Modern Art, New York / Drawings: Recent Acquisitions Plantin Press: 1967 (Box 2)
  - Barr, Alfred H., Jr. / Picasso 75th Anniversary Exhibition The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1957 (Box 2)
  - Penrose, Roland / Portrait of Picasso The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1957 (Box 2)
  - The Museum of Modern Art, New York / Painting and Sculpture Acquisitions The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1960 (Box 2)
  - Wiesenthal, M. / Yucatan and the Maya Civilization Geocolor S.A.: 1978 (Box 2)
  - Bush, Martin H. / Boris Lovet-Lorski: The Language of Time The Barnes Printing Co. Inc., New York: 1967 (Box 2)
  - L’estrange, Sir Roger / Fables of Aesop Dover Publications, Inc., New York: 1967 (Box 2)
  - Bennet, Wendell C. / Ancient Arts of the Andes The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1954 (Box 2)
  - The Furniture and the Sculpture of Wharton Esherick Thistle Press, New York: 1958 (Box 2)
  - Lieberman, William S. / The Sculptor’s Studio: Etchings by Picasso The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1952 (Box 2)
  - Rand, Paul / Thoughts on Design Wittenborn and Company, New York: 1947 (Box 2)
  - Stuttgart / Design Center Design Center Stuttgart: 1969 (Box 2)
  - Vincent Van Gogh: Paintings, Watercolors and Drawings C. Huig Ltd. Zaandam, The Netherlands: 1964 (Box 2)
  - Pedretti, Carlo / Leonardo: A Study In Chronology and Style Johnson Reprint Corporation: 1982 (Box 2)
  - Connections: The Work of Charles and Ray Eames UCLA Art Council: 1976 (Box 2)
  - Saunders, J.B. deC. M. And Charles D. O’Malley / The Illustrations of Andreas Vesalius The World Publishing Company: 1950 / of Brussels (Box 2)
  - Tony Sarg’s New York Greenberg, Publisher, New York: 1926 (Box 2)
  - The New City: Architecture and Urban Renewal The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1967 (Box 3)
  - Hulten, K.G. Pontus / The Machine as Seen at the End of the Mechanical Age The Museum of Modern Art, New York: 1968 (Box 3)
  - Benes, Oldrich / Czechoslovakia: Ancient and Modern Orbis, Prague: 1967 (Box 3)
  - Bettmann, Otto L. / Bettmann Portable Archive Picture House Press, Inc.: 1966 (Box 3)
  - Design Forecast Aluminum Company of America: 1959 (Box 3)
  - Nelson, George / Display Whitney Publications, Inc., New York: 1953 (Box 3)
  - Nelson, George / Living Spaces Whitney Publications, Inc., New York: 1952 (Box 3)
  - Museo D’arte Antica al Castello Sforzesco Estratto Dalla Rivista, Cita Di Milano: 1957 (Box 3)
  - Malone, Robert / The Robert Book Push Pin Press: 1978 (Box 3)
  - Sawyer, Aln R. / Mastercraft of Ancient Peru The Solomon R. Guggenheim Foundation, New York: 1968 (Box 3)
  - Steichen, Edward / The Family of Man Simon and Schuster: 1955 (Box 3)
  - Zahle, Erik / A Treasury of Scandinavian Design Golden Press, New York: 1961 (Box 3)
  - The Artist in America W.W. Norton and Company, Inc., New York: 1967 (Box 3)
  - Paintings from the Huntington Hartford Collection in the Gallery of Modern Art The Foundation for Modern Art, Inc.: 1964 (Box 3)
  - Alexander Calder: A Retrospective Exhibition The Solomon R. Guggenheim foundation, New York: 1964 (Box 3)
  - Steichen, Edward / The Family of Man Maco Magazine Corporation: 1955 (Box 3)
  - Society of Industrial Designers / Industrial Design in America: 1954 Farrar, Straus and Young, Inc., New York: 1954 (Box 3)
  - Duncan, David Douglas / The Private World of Pablo Picasso The Ridge Press: 1958 (Box 3)
  - Taylor, Francis Henry / Fifty Centuries of Art Harper and Brothers, New York: 1954 (Box 3)
  - Bacher, Otto H. / With Whistler in Venice The Century Co., New York: 1909 (Box 3)